<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VSM\'22</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="CryptoCurrency">
        <item>@string/Crypto01</item>

    </string-array>
    <string name="None">Select One</string>
    <string name="Crypto01">Cheems Coin</string>
    <string name="Crypto02">Surreal Coin</string>
    <string name="Crypto03">Pepe Coin</string>

    <!--    //Headings-->
    <string name="heading_one">What is VSM? </string>
    <string name="heading_two">Stocks and Theme</string>
    <string name="heading_three">Trade based on news</string>
    <string name="heading_fourth">Use Powercards to increase your chances</string>

    <!--    //Description-->
    <string name="desc_one">Virtual Stock Market is fun and realistical way of presenting the stock market through a defined storyline. With prices rising and falling every round let us see who will be the next Harshad Mehta.</string>
    <string name="desc_two">In Virtual Stock Market we have included fun stocks related to our theme of Mafia like guns, oils and much more. So get ready to experience this simulation of the stock market.</string>
    <string name="desc_three">With continuous news which you will receive from the Mafia Times regarding the shady deals of mafia. Use your gut and invest to maximize the profit and be the winner.  </string>
    <string name="desc_fourth">We have some promising powercards which will make your life easy as a trader. With Loan-a-cap and Insider Trading you can select the perfect stock for your victory.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_on_boarding">OnBoardingActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="desc">trade_o_live is educating people across India about Stock Market Trading and Investing Since 2021 . The Founder and CEO , Mr Priyanshu Shirsat has won IFA ( Youngest Entrepreneur In Stock Market 2021) and has 5+ years of experience in stock market. We have trained 500+ Traders and Investors . Featured on ZEE BUSINESS (IFA AWARDS 2021)</string>
    <string name="dsc_title">In this course you will learn how human psychology plays an important role in Stock Market</string>
    <string name="desc_ps">As a trader you must have gone through emotions. The course will help you to control your emotions during the trading and reduce your losses while making your overall portfolio</string>

</resources>
